["ABELYANA" BY MAKI PLAYING]
Enrico.
It's way past your 10-day deadline
with Boss Zandro.
I've sent Zandro 20,000 pesos.
You owe him 20,000 dollars.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- [BLOWS LAND]
[THUG GROANS]
[PANTING]
[PANICKED SHOUTS]
Help!
Let's take him to the hospital!
Okay. Will it be possible to do
in eight weeks?
Six weeks.
Very confident, Mr. Valentin.
Then we have a deal.
- Sir Andy, thank you.
- Yeah.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
[BILLY] Thank you. Thank you.
Gosh, what would I do
if I didn't have
my ridiculously cocky best friend?
He's talented, handsome, and smells good!
He's perfect!
All he's missing is a girlfriend.
We'll find one for him. Mm!
[NURSE] May I speak
with Benilda Cariño?
[BILLY] Who's this?
Ma'am, this is Nurse Anj
from St. John Hospital.
You're listed as an emergency contact.
For patient Enrico Dominguez.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
What's your relationship to the patient?
[BILLY] I can't believe he put me down
as his emergency contact.
What was he expecting?
You went to see him.
You even paid his bill.
Of course I had to pay for it. Otherwise,
the hospital might come after me later.
[MAN] So you're Enrico's daughter.
Your father owes my boss
a huge sum of money.
Over a million pesos.
It's his debt, not mine.
He doesn't have the money to pay it back.
Then he shouldn't have borrowed
the money in the first place.
And your boss
shouldn't have lent it to him.
Wait a minute.
- Hey!
- Jordan!
- That's your problem!
My friend has nothing to do with it, okay?
- Come on, let's just go.
- Okay?!
- That's enough! Jordan!
- Let go!
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SIGHS] No…
- [PHONE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Hey.
I just called to check if you're okay.
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me.
How could I not?
Look.
I just thought you should know.
I'm at the police station.
What? What are you doing there?
I don't want to add to your problems,
but I'm sure sooner or later,
you'll find out anyway.
[JORDAN] I just found out
Bea got off the hook again.
Caloy denies that they were accomplices.
What?
How did that happen?
Of course, Caloy would deny it.
Aren't there other ways to check?
What about Caloy's phone?
They didn't find a phone on Caloy.
He probably discarded it.
With Bea…
I'm sorry, dude.
[JORDAN] They didn't find anything.
They're meticulous.
So, I came.
I had to try and do something.
Jordan, don't put yourself
in danger again, okay?
No. I promise.
I'll be safe.
Anyway, that's it.
I didn't want to stress you out. Okay?
So relax.
Okay.
Thank you.
Please, be careful over there, okay?
I'll keep you posted.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[JORDAN] Okay.
Cooperate with us.
Then we could consider
dropping your other cases.
I won't fall for your trap.
But you already have, haven't you?
Caloy.
Bea abandoned you.
Why are you still protecting her?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you talking about?
Bea has nothing to do with this.
I did it on my own.
Because I love her.
You planned this.
But why did you target Billy?
Hmm?
Why?!
I don't know.
[TENSE MUSIC FADING]
Oh, it's already late.
[BEA] Uh…
Ma!
I'm a supervisor,
so I can clock in at any time.
Oh.
Sorry, dear.
The landlord came earlier.
She was asking for the rent.
I told her,
"Don't be impatient!
My daughter will pay you."
"She might even slap you with her money!"
[CHUCKLES] That's right, Ma.
[BEA] I won't just slap her with it.
I'll choke her with my money.
[MARIELA CHUCKLES]
Okay, I'll get going then.
All right.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BILLY] Auntie Pres.
Oh, Billy! I'm sorry.
- I forgot to call you.
- It's okay.
They said Sir Eric couldn't
come in to work today.
Huh? It's okay.
But it's a shame
this will be wasted, Auntie Pres.
Billy, are you all right?
I went to the hospital earlier,
Auntie Pres.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why?
Thank you.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Who paid for it?
Your daughter did.
- She came here?
- Mm.
You were asleep when she visited you.
Did she know about this?
No, sir.
Thank you.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BILLY] The bill has been paid,
but please,
don't make me your emergency contact
because next time, I won't be coming.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Your father really is the worst.
He even got you involved in his debts.
I'm not surprised anymore, Auntie Pres.
When I found out that he became
a scammer in Canada,
I already knew that
he was only after money.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Can you still handle it?
Of course.
What if he comes back?
Especially when he finds out that
you paid for his hospital bill,
he might get the wrong idea
and think that you care about him.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's the first and last time
that I'll help him, Auntie Pres.
Let's just leave it at that.
There are more important things
that I need to take care of
before that man.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why can't I go upstairs?!
We really can't let you, ma'am.
We were told not to let you go upstairs.
Who said that?
Miss, I didn't do anything wrong!
Why can't I--
[HEELS CLACKING]
Ms. Talia! Ms. Talia!
What are you doing here?
I thought you were in jail!
What? I've done nothing wrong!
You were working together with that thief!
No! That's not true!
- Whoever said that--
- Security, take her outside!
- Ms. Talia, I just need a job!
- Now, go!
- I'm begging you, Ms. Talia! Please!
- Please leave, ma'am.
- Ms. Talia!
- Billy?
Bea's here and she's making a scene.
I thought our plan would put her in jail.
Unfortunately, Ms. Talia,
we still don't have substantial evidence
linking her to the robbery.
Her claims to the police
are still consistent
that Carlos Toledo was harassing her.
We planned this!
What are we going to do now?
Don't worry, Ms. Talia,
you've helped enough.
Leave it to me now.
Okay, Billy.
Whatever you need, just tell me.
Okay. Thank you so much, Ms. Talia.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Marj!
[MARJ] Hm?
Hey.
We need to talk.
It's about your vlog.
[MARJ] What's wrong with it?
[VALERIE] It's missing something!
You should've also mentioned
his partner-in-crime, Bea Mercado.
- Stop resisting!
- [CALOY] Hold on.
- [OFFICER] Get in!
- [CALOY GRUNTING] Sir…
- [SIGHS]
- [OFFICER] Let's go!
Justice said "not today"
and karma handled it.
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
You're right!
You know, I can't believe that
she was released again.
[VALERIE] It's fine.
Let's just make another vlog about it.
Okay. Let's do it.
And we'll let the world know
that she's also a criminal.
Yeah.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Did Jordan really think…
[CHUCKLES]
…he could outsmart me of all people?
Ah, it hurts.
That's because you weren't careful.
For heaven's sake, Caloy!
What is wrong with you?!
Every single one of your plans fails!
You messed up again!
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What are you doing here?
Can you please talk to your people?
Let the world know that I'm a criminal?!
Maybe they want to know
what a real criminal is.
Why?
Aren't you one?
So true.
Even our own house isn't safe
from your anger.
Neither is my family.
Do you think you're going to scare me?
Enjoy your freedom
because it won't last long.
Oh! And by the way…
Orange looks good on you.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES STIRRING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Ma!
Uh,
do you want to eat out?
So we've sealed a partnership
with Cipher Axis Security System.
They will officially provide us
- our cybersecurity.
- [MARJ] Ooh!
And given that,
I asked them to be one of our partners
for our Happily Ever After events.
They said yes.
And they assured us that
their system is secure.
So congrats, team!
- Yay!
You did this while you were planning
what to do with Caloy?
[VAL] As if Bea wasn't harassing
us just now.
[SHUSHING]
- It's okay. We won anyway.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
WHAT HAPPENED WITH THESE GUYS?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Charm, what's wrong?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Ralph's mom sent this.
[CHARM BREATHES DEEPLY]
They saw it.
And now, they're questioning me
if they did the right thing
when they invested in us.
But what's worse is,
they're questioning
my relationship with Ralph.
[SOBS] They said
that we're involved with criminals.
That we're a part of them.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Billy, sorry. I'm sorry.
Just what am I doing?
This is nothing compared
to what you're going through.
- I'm sorry.
- Charm, don't be like that.
There are no big or small problems
between friends, okay?
- [SNIFFLES]
- Just let it all out.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's okay.
[SNIFFLES]
[TONI] It's okay.
[CHARM SOBS]
[SNIFFLING, EXHALES HEAVILY]
- [BILLY] Whoo-hoo!
- [CHARM] Group hug!
[LAUGHING]
Just ignore those posts, okay?
[SNIFFLES]
I'm still looking for a way
to trace Bea's father.
I tried getting a copy
of her birth certificate,
but it'll need an SPA or a court order.
When I went to see Caloy,
he still denies that Bea is involved.
For an entrapment where both of them
should've been locked up.
[JORDAN EXHALES HEAVILY]
I tried to ask
what the real reason is for all this.
If it's just for money.
It's not about money.
If it were, they would've asked
for some a long time ago.
What? They're just like my father?
They think I'm an ATM machine?
Hold on.
I'll just withdraw some money.
[IMITATING ATM BEEPING SOUNDS]
[JORDAN] Oops. I have zero balance.
I don't get it!
How do so many girls fall
for your lame jokes!
- What the hell?
- [THUDS]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHISPERING] Is she okay?
I thought you couldn't get to work today.
Is everything okay?
I got to fix my family emergency.
[PRECIOUS] Mmm.
I got to talk to my kids.
It's okay now.
Oh. That's good.
Oh, by the way,
Billy wanted to give this to you.
She was here earlier.
You just missed each other.
She said thanks for everything.
[PRECIOUS] And it's diabetic-friendly.
Billy knows.
Thanks.
- She really didn't have to.
- [PRECIOUS TSKS]
Well, she said it's
to thank you for everything.
Actually, she's already been here twice,
but you just keep missing each other.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Yeah, it's a shame.
Don't worry. There's always next time.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING, FADES]
I can't believe his mom
is still that controlling.
Well, I'd rather have a controlling parent
than one who doesn't care.
Not everyone has a parent
who worries about them.
You have a point.
I should be the one
handling this, Ma!
It was Benilda Cariño herself
who invited me out for dinner.
Ma, the legal issues
are not directly connected to LoveList.
Now, I just want to know if the CEO
of LoveList is a decent woman.
[MARIELA] That Billy thinks
that she can just treat you
like you're nothing.
That's why I told you
to just trust me, Ma.
I have a reservation under Billy Cariño.
[MARIELA] Are you following
my daughter?!
Cat got your tongue?
I'm not following your daughter.
How dare you?!
Like I told you before,
it's your daughter
you need to talk to.
Let go of my mother.